Hi and welcome to my new video about this collar from Swedish collar and I'm
going to tell you what I think of it and I'm going to show you how to use this as
a key for opening and closing it. This collar was gifted to me by Swedish collar
so I have to declare this video as advertisement video but nevertheless I'm
I'm going to tell you my own opinion and since a lot of you asked on my Instagram account about my opinion and about some details, I'm going to do this video.
To open this color you don't need a key or screwdriver but this little piece of plastic
which is basically a magnet and you put it there and you press the whole plate with the
magnet up until it clicks once.
Then you can put this away and you see that the collar opens.
To close it again you push this plate up until it clicks.
So unlike other collars this is made from two solid blocks, from two solid halves.
It's purely made of milled aluminium so no welding, no bending, just really heavy metal.
The front plate and the ring and this little attachment thing, they're solid brass.
They're also CNC milled, really solid.
There are other types of colors from Swedish Color and so this is like the light one.
Speaking about weight, this is super heavy.
It's nearly 700 gram and if you put it around your neck you'll feel this weight.
So when I wore it for the first time it was for a few hours and after that I realized
on the next day that my muscles have been sore because the weight was not something
I was used to and my muscles in my neck had to work a bit to support it.
So some of you may see it as a disadvantage that it's so heavy but others may say that's
the good thing about it.
I think everyone has to decide it for himself or herself.
It's a good fit though because it's oval and it's not around circumference so it's more
comfortable to wear.
It really is comfortable even though it's heavy.
If you lose the magnet though, there is no second key or whatever and if it's an emergency
you have to go to the hardware store and buy another magnet to open it again, which may
be a disadvantage.
So take care of your open thingy, opener.
what else? About the price I got a lot of messages asking about the price or a lot
of comments on the price and I have to say it is expensive and to be honest I
wouldn't have bought it myself because I'm not that much into all-time wearing
colors or that kind of stuff but if you're aiming for a really high quality
like state-of-the-art because this is like the best I've seen so far. I hold it
in my hands and was like this is amazing. So if you're ready to invest for a
lifetime color so to say then you should probably go with this because it is
really good. I mostly use it as a shooting high-end accessory. You can wear
it as statement piece or you can use it the way you see it fit.
It's so warm.
I've been wearing collars a lot before I got this one and I frequently use them for shootings,
for styling.
This one is really lightweight compared and a completely different look.
But I also got some PVC ones with rivets or with multiple rings and D-rings.
And before I got this one this was like the heavy color or the heaviest I owned.
And yeah.
I still like it, I still like all the other ones and I really like this one so it's all about
its purpose and the occasion you want to wear it for and also a bit about the outfit.
If you don't mind bearing the weight you can wear it for clubbing as well.
I probably won't wear it for clubbing I will go with a lighter more metal
version I don't know. Of course it's not only a statement accessory but if you're
more into rubber and stuff like that it also looks good over latex and you can
combine it with your favorite pieces. I think the next shooting I'll do with the
color is going to be one with latex and some cool accessories matching the color.
So casual style just top and fits as well it's more of even more of an eye catcher
than if the other clothes are plain. Okay that was it thanks for watching I
I hope you enjoyed this video. Please subscribe to see more videos and have a nice day.